[{"answer": "  Gee, thanks a lot", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Where are you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " No. The little one", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "They're weird names", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "The best", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend, you are never out of your head", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hot. Where do I sign", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Tan? What tan? It faded on the airplane. I'd try to get my money back, but who do you ask?  Two hundred dollars a night, for what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Well, I'll miss riding home with you. I was looking forward to it", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I enjoy crushing into you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Kids on a joy ride. Happens all the time", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Come on. What were they, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'd like to speak to Dr. my friend, please", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "New? He's been here for years", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How did it happen", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Blew up? What do you mean it blew up", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " You know, you got a strange line here", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Short? It's ended", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " my friend", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I see", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " my friend?  What are you doing ... ", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It was the window", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Me neither. Nothing too exciting. So tell me, to what do I owe the honor", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Shit, my friend. I'd love to see you. But I'm kind of laid up here. I've been sick", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " I need to see you, my friend", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " I need to see you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know who they are, or what they are. But they're gonna get me and I'm scared, my friend. I'm so scared I can't do anything. I can't go to my sisters. I can't even go home", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "They're waitin' for me, that's why", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's okay, my friend. It's okay", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Don't do anything.  my friend, I know what you're talking about", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " You've seen them", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Bullshit. Someone's covering somethin'. That was no accident", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Cars don't explode that way. Any simpleton knows that", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Not my head, buddy. Not me. I'm gettin' a headache just listenin' to you", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I say you should get a shrink", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Doctor.  Ph.D", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I am", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Ah! I thought you were a mailman", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Then why aren't you teaching? Why aren't you in a university", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Well, try, huh", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Things happen? What the fuck are you talking about? They did something to us, my friend. We have to expose this", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Maybe there's a larger truth", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Maybe the demons are real", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Goddamn it. What kind of bullshit is that", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What the hell is that supposed to mean", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " War games? that place? That's not true! How can you believe that? Can't you see what they're doing? It's all a lie. We were in my friend, for God's sake. You've got to believe me", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Take me home", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Dead? No. I just hurt my back. I'm not dead", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I'm alive", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I don't know. I don't know.  This isn't happening", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Then what are you doing here", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What isn't happening", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I was in Hell. I've been there. It's horrible. I don't want to die, my friend", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I've seen it. It's all pain", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I'm walking, aren't I", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Not tonight, my friend. No more rest", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "It might be for me", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " Hello ... No. He's not here. I haven't seen him all night ... I don't know when ... What? Tell him what?  that place? ... What experiments", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "None of us can remember that night. I get flashes of it but they don't make sense. We saw shrinks for years. But nothing they did could ever touch it. What happened? Was there ever an offensive", "docId": "JacobsLadder.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "But there was an attack. I can still see them coming. There was a fight, wasn't there", "qsentId": 62}]